[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent", "40 percent"]}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Who are the 1 percent?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "1", "percent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, the 1 percent, they have about 40 percent of all the wealth in this country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "1", "percent", ",", "they", "have", "about", "40", "percent", "of", "all", "the", "wealth", "in", "this", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Is this really a protest against capitalism, as some have been saying, or is it a protest against capitalist greed and abuse of capitalism?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "really", "a", "protest", "against", "capitalism", ",", "as", "some", "have", "been", "saying", ",", "or", "is", "it", "a", "protest", "against", "capitalist", "greed", "and", "abuse", "of", "capitalism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, it depends on who you asked.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "depends", "on", "who", "you", "asked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "What's wrong with me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "You're in the 1 percent, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "in", "the", "1", "percent", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "I'm not in the 1 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "in", "the", "1", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Probably 0.2 percent?", "question_tokens": ["Probably", "0.2", "percent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["0.2 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "You're not in if 1 percent?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "in", "if", "1", "percent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Of course I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "How can I be in the 1 percent?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "I", "be", "in", "the", "1", "percent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Because you're worth millions.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "you", "'re", "worth", "millions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Well, then if you believe that about me, then that's really something, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "then", "if", "you", "believe", "that", "about", "me", ",", "then", "that", "'s", "really", "something", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "No, I'm asking if you accept that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "asking", "if", "you", "accept", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Where is Monica?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "Monica", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Hi.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "answer", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Well, for me, I mean, I am a person with a master's degree who has been unemployed since I graduated.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "me", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "am", "a", "person", "with", "a", "master", "'s", "degree", "who", "has", "been", "unemployed", "since", "I", "graduated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Are there lots of people to blame?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "lots", "of", "people", "to", "blame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "I think there is some of that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "is", "some", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "If you were slicing a pie up, how would you fairly do it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "slicing", "a", "pie", "up", ",", "how", "would", "you", "fairly", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "But just a sense of where you think the majority of blame lies here?", "question_tokens": ["But", "just", "a", "sense", "of", "where", "you", "think", "the", "majority", "of", "blame", "lies", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "As far as blaming the American people, I mean, haven't they been through enough really?", "question_tokens": ["As", "far", "as", "blaming", "the", "American", "people", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "have", "n't", "they", "been", "through", "enough", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, they have.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Nobody went against probably all the guidelines from their parents?", "question_tokens": ["Nobody", "went", "against", "probably", "all", "the", "guidelines", "from", "their", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "I mean there has to be some sense of self-blame, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "there", "has", "to", "be", "some", "sense", "of", "self-blame", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "And what is the simple answer to getting America back to work?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "the", "simple", "answer", "to", "getting", "America", "back", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, it's one of the answers, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "answers", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What is your view of the jobs crisis and where the president now is on this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "the", "jobs", "crisis", "and", "where", "the", "president", "now", "is", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, I think that it's very hard to find a job, no matter what you've got, whether you have a high school education or a master's.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "very", "hard", "to", "find", "a", "job", ",", "no", "matter", "what", "you", "'ve", "got", ",", "whether", "you", "have", "a", "high", "school", "education", "or", "a", "master", "'s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "What's your gut feeling?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "gut", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I think computers have changed the world.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "computers", "have", "changed", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "What do you do about the fact that computers can now do, in some cases, the jobs of a thousand people?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "computers", "can", "now", "do", ",", "in", "some", "cases", ",", "the", "jobs", "of", "a", "thousand", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Well, first of all, that's a good thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Why are they holding on to the money?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "they", "holding", "on", "to", "the", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What's been your concern?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "your", "concern", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "My biggest concern, obviously, I'm not going to be able to find a job.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "biggest", "concern", ",", "obviously", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "be", "able", "to", "find", "a", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "How much debt have you wracked up?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "debt", "have", "you", "wracked", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I'll be close to probably 50, 60,000.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "be", "close", "to", "probably", "50", ",", "60,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "And you know how can America compete if the brains of the country are being treated in this way?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "know", "how", "can", "America", "compete", "if", "the", "brains", "of", "the", "country", "are", "being", "treated", "in", "this", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "And where they have to go out into the real world at 22 years old or 24 with this crushing debt.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "where", "they", "have", "to", "go", "out", "into", "the", "real", "world", "at", "22", "years", "old", "or", "24", "with", "this", "crushing", "debt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Now you've come from a country where -- you know, how much debt do students have when they're 23 years old and they leave university?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "you", "'ve", "come", "from", "a", "country", "where", "--", "you", "know", ",", "how", "much", "debt", "do", "students", "have", "when", "they", "'re", "23", "years", "old", "and", "they", "leave", "university", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Well, I see increasingly a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "see", "increasingly", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Or a city school here, huh?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "a", "city", "school", "here", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "A thousand dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "thousand", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "If I were president -- and I'm not announcing, by the way, on your show.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "were", "president", "--", "and", "I", "'m", "not", "announcing", ",", "by", "the", "way", ",", "on", "your", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "I mean would she be better off being poorer?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "would", "she", "be", "better", "off", "being", "poorer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Well, you haven't been poor.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "n't", "been", "poor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "They wouldn't get the funding, wouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "would", "n't", "get", "the", "funding", ",", "would", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "They would get -- they would get no help and they would have Republican candidates saying, well, that's your own problem.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "would", "get", "--", "they", "would", "get", "no", "help", "and", "they", "would", "have", "Republican", "candidates", "saying", ",", "well", ",", "that", "'s", "your", "own", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "How important is the tax issue?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "the", "tax", "issue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "It's very important.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Because the wealthy have not been paying their fair share.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "the", "wealthy", "have", "not", "been", "paying", "their", "fair", "share", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 527, "question": "What was wrong with the way we used to have it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "wrong", "with", "the", "way", "we", "used", "to", "have", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Well, no, I mean --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", ",", "I", "mean", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "VB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Really, what was wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Really", ",", "what", "was", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Let's not be too --", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "not", "be", "too", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "With that?", "question_tokens": ["With", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Let's not be too rose tipped it, because there would be people from previous generations who will have a myriad of problems, too.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "not", "be", "too", "rose", "tipped", "it", ",", "because", "there", "would", "be", "people", "from", "previous", "generations", "who", "will", "have", "a", "myriad", "of", "problems", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "What is a good capitalist?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "a", "good", "capitalist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Well, the thing, again, when we were growing up, there was a system that said -- I mean the way I described it, I think I might have said this last time I was on the show, that the contract with the workers, between the workers and the owners was that if you the worker have worked hard and the company prospered, you prospered.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "thing", ",", "again", ",", "when", "we", "were", "growing", "up", ",", "there", "was", "a", "system", "that", "said", "--", "I", "mean", "the", "way", "I", "described", "it", ",", "I", "think", "I", "might", "have", "said", "this", "last", "time", "I", "was", "on", "the", "show", ",", "that", "the", "contract", "with", "the", "workers", ",", "between", "the", "workers", "and", "the", "owners", "was", "that", "if", "you", "the", "worker", "have", "worked", "hard", "and", "the", "company", "prospered", ",", "you", "prospered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Who do you blame?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "blame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I blame myself part of it, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "blame", "myself", "part", "of", "it", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Do you have any confidence that people are going to come up with answers to get you out of this problem?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "confidence", "that", "people", "are", "going", "to", "come", "up", "with", "answers", "to", "get", "you", "out", "of", "this", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "What do you think has happened to the American dream?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "has", "happened", "to", "the", "American", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Yes, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Yes, I mean, my loan was, you know, underperforming.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "my", "loan", "was", ",", "you", "know", ",", "underperforming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Mr. Perkins?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Perkins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Hello.", "answer_tokens": ["Hello", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Perkins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Is the message clear?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "message", "clear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "I think that their message should be more defined.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "their", "message", "should", "be", "more", "defined", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "How big a part of this is disquiet and concern over health care in this country, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "big", "a", "part", "of", "this", "is", "disquiet", "and", "concern", "over", "health", "care", "in", "this", "country", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Well, I think a lot of it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "I mean this is -- this is -- we're not going to take this anymore, we're not going to listen to this kind of argument because these are the victims of this and they are -- and fortunately -- can I just say one thing -- good news?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "this", "is", "--", "this", "is", "--", "we", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "take", "this", "anymore", ",", "we", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "listen", "to", "this", "kind", "of", "argument", "because", "these", "are", "the", "victims", "of", "this", "and", "they", "are", "--", "and", "fortunately", "--", "can", "I", "just", "say", "one", "thing", "--", "good", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "RB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "Mr. Mooney?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Mooney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mooney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "You know, you know how all Americans feel or just how you feel in California?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "you", "know", "how", "all", "Americans", "feel", "or", "just", "how", "you", "feel", "in", "California", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PDT", "NNPS", "NN", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Michigan"]}, "docId": "111025pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Very quickly, Michael, your response?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "quickly", ",", "Michael", ",", "your", "response", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "I live in Michigan, thank you, though.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "live", "in", "Michigan", ",", "thank", "you", ",", "though", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}]